acornonline.com 2016-11-30

# Acorn Privacy Policy at Acorn

Welcome to the **Acorn Online** site (the **"Site"** ), operated by **Universal Screen Arts, Inc.** , a catalog and ecommerce company ( **"Universal Screen Arts," "Universal," "we,"** or **"our"** ). 

As used in this Privacy Policy, **Acorn Online** includes **Universal** and its affiliated family of companies including **Bas Bleu, Catalog Classics, Signals, Support Plus, Wireless, What On Earth** and any other future affiliated or related companies or brands. For a complete list of all Universal’s businesses, please visit us at **[UniversalScreenArts.com](http://www.universalscreenarts.com/)**. 

We respect your opinion and choice regarding your privacy online and offline. The Privacy Policy discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our Site ( **[ACORNONLINE.COM](http://www.acornonline.com/)** ). It also governs any other information-gathering, use, or dissemination practices related to information collected from you (sometimes referred to as a "visitor," "user," "you," or "your") directly through or from the Site, or from telephone, facsimile, postal mail, personal delivery, or other additional offline means or media. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into our Terms of Use, which must be reviewed and accepted by you as a condition of use of the Site. The Site is not intended for children under the age of 18. It does not knowingly collect personal information online from visitors in this age group, and we will delete information from a person in that age group as quickly as possible upon receipt of notice that such information has been collected. 

If you have any questions regarding privacy issues after consulting this page please contact us at: 

**Acorn**  
5581 Hudson Industrial Parkway  
PO Box 2599  
Hudson, OH 44236-0099  
Orders: 1-844-734-8468  
Fax: 1-800-950-9569  

**What information is collected and how is it used when I visit Acorn Online?**  
Our Site automatically recognizes the home server of visitors. We may also employ a third-party tracking service that enables enhancement to major search engine marketing programs. We may use this information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site or sites of our affiliated companies. In addition, we may aggregate information on the pages that you access or visit and use the information to improve the content of our Site. 

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of the Site. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We receive and store information you submit to us through our Site or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information (as addressed below), but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. For example, if you make a purchase using a credit card, we will need to collect information such as your credit card number and billing address to complete that transaction. 

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Our authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information (see below), and the page you requested. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our servers, analyze trends and administer the Site. We may also collect and display the total counts that a page has been viewed. Certain third-party programs are available to help you to visit websites anonymously. While we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available. 

**What are "Cookies" and how are they used?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages of the Site are visited and by how many people. We also use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart. 

Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We do not override these settings or options, including any "Do Not Track" settings. However, if you utilize the aforementioned privacy features, you may be unable to obtain certain content, features, services, products, or benefits on the Site. 

**What information do you collect when I place an order, request a catalog or other information?**  
When placing an order for merchandise or for a catalog or general information, we request and collect as necessary your: e-mail address, name, street address, delivery address if different, City/Sate/Zip, telephone number and credit card number and expiration date ( orders only ). 

We may use this information for limited purposes, including recordkeeping, editorial and feedback purposes, content improvement, or to customize the content and layout of the Site. We may also send out e-mails with news, products, offers, surveys or promotions that we believe may be of interest to you. Personally identifying information voluntarily provided to us by you may be added to our databases and used for future contact regarding updates to the Site or new services provided by us. From time to time, we may need to contact you concerning information you submitted to us. You agree that we may use the personal information voluntarily provided by you for us to contact you. 

Except as specifically set forth herein, any personally-identifying information that you provide to us through the Site will not be disclosed to other third party entities not affiliated with us except that certain personally-identifying information may be shared with Acorn Online ([www.acorn.tv](http://www.acorn.tv/)) or its parent RLJ Entertainment ([www.rljentertainment.com](http://www.rljentertainment.com/) ). Additionally, our personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to your information if necessary in the normal course of our business. 

**How will we use the information you provide?**  
The information we receive allows us to tailor our product offer and improve your shopping experience, making shopping easier and more enjoyable. It also enables us to process your purchases, confirm your orders, customize the content and layout of our pages, notify you about updates to our websites and products, and provide you with marketing information. 

The information you supply to us is added to our customer database. You may receive periodic mailings from us about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events. If you do not want to receive such mailings from us, please contact us at the address, telephone numbers, Fax number or e-mail above and specify "Do Not Mail Acorn Online Catalog" in your communication along with your exact name and address. 

We employ a third-party tracking service that enables us to improve the way we market through the major search engines. 

We may share contact information and other data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with any Universal Screen Arts. We may share your information with our business partners and third party companies and other organizations that may interest you. These companies and organizations may use the information we share to contact you for their own marketing purposes. Should Acorn Online merge with, acquire or be acquired by another business entity, some or all of your information could be transferred to the other entity. We may disclose your personal information when Acorn Online believes it is necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request or to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Acorn Online, our customers or the public as required or permitted by law. If you do not wish to receive mailings from other third party companies, please contact us at the address, telephone numbers, Fax number or e-mail above and specify "Do Not Rent Address to Third Party" in your communication along with your exact name and address. 

We periodically email our customer list about new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such emails in the future, simply click the "unsubscribe" link on any promotional email you receive from us, or click the link below. 

**How will my telephone number be used?**  
Acorn Online will contact you by telephone only in the event that the need arises to communicate with you directly regarding the processing of your order or inquiry. 

On limited occasions, we may contact you to survey your shopping experience. 

Telephone numbers are not shared with third parties. 

**How will my credit card number be used?**  
You credit card number and expiration are used to process your current transaction. 

For your security and ours, we do not store credit card information on our online server. 

**Updates to our policy.**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to Opt-out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

**Security.**  
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. 

**Third Party Websites.**  
The Site may also contain links to third party websites. The Site may contain links to other websites for the convenience of users in locating information, products, or services that may be of interest. If you access a third party website from a link on this Site, any information you disclose on that website is not subject to this Privacy Policy. It is possible that these links may be used by third parties or others to collect personal or other information about you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites, advertisers, or third parties or the content of such websites and it is your sole obligation to review and understand the privacy practices and policies of these other websites. We do not control these third parties' use of cookies, collection of information, or how they manage such information. It is solely your obligation to review and understand the privacy practices and policies of these other websites, advertisers and any third parties. 

**Children's Information.**  
We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. The Site is not designed or intended to attract children under the age of 18. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is under the age of 18. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.**  
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to this Site. Your continued use of this Site after any changes have been posted indicates your agreement to the revised terms. Accordingly, we urge you to review this Privacy Policy at the start of each use of this Site. We will also list the date of the last revision at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. 

**Confidentiality and Security.**  
We use modern technology to protect the information you submit. All personally identifiable user information is stored on secured servers and behind a firewall. However, no security system is completely impenetrable, so we cannot guarantee the absolute security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. We are not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet. 

**Your California Privacy Rights.**  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (also known as the "Shine The Light" law) permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third-parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request to: 

**Acorn**  
5581 Hudson Industrial Parkway  
PO Box 2599  
Hudson, OH 44236-0099  
Orders: 1-844-734-8468  
Fax: 1-800-950-9569
